const STORE = [
  {
      question: "What animal was found in Pete's percolator?",
      answers: [
      'squirrel',
      'fish',
      'crawdad',
      'spider'
      ],
      correctAnswer: 'fish',
  },
  {
      question: "What was Agent Cooper urged to drink before it cooled?",
      answers: [
          'coffee',
          'tea',
          'milk',
          'healing tonic'
      ],
      correctAnswer: 'milk',
  },
  {
      question: "What nursery-rhyme-style song did Leland Palmer sing?",
      answers: [
          'Michael Finnegan Begin Again',
          'Mairzy Doats',
          'Itsy Bitsy Spider',
          'Old MacDonald'
      ],
      correctAnswer: 'Mairzy Doats',
  },
  {
      question: "What flower symbolized a mysterious case for the FBI agents?",
      answers: [
          'yellow carnation',
          'purple hydrangea',
          'blue rose',
          'pink tulip'
      ],
      correctAnswer: 'blue rose',
  },
  {
      question: "Who was Bobby Briggs buying his cocaine from?",
      answers: [
          'Leland Palmer',
          'Benjamine Horne',
          'Hank Jennings',
          'Leo Johnson'
        ],
        correctAnswer: 'Leo Johnson',
    },
    {
      question: "What was the name of the one-armed man?",
      answers: [
          'Windom',
          'Hank',
          'John',
          'Mike'
      ],
        correctAnswer: 'Mike',
    },
    {
      question: "Who was Big Ed Hurley's secret love?",
      answers: [
          'Log Lady',
          'Norma Jennings',
          'Audrey Horne',
          'Lawrence Jacoby'
      ],
        correctAnswer: 'Norma Jennings',
    },
    {
      question: "What happened to Josie after she got shot?",
      answers: [
          'Died',
          'Became a ghost',
          'Disappeared into a lightning strike',
          'Turned into a doorknob'
      ],
        correctAnswer: 'Turned into a doorknob',
    },
    {
      question: "Who does Dale Cooper address his voice memos to?",
      answers: [
          'Diane',
          'Lucy',
          'Laura Palmer',
          'FBI Director Gordon Cole'
      ],
        correctAnswer: 'Diane',
    },
    {
      question: "Who killed Laura Palmer?",
      answers: [
          'Sheriff Truman/Bob',
          'James Hurley/Bob',
          'Leo Johnson/Bob',
          'Leland Palmer/Bob'
      ],
        correctAnswer: 'Leland Palmer/Bob',
    }
  ]